Batel Alemayehu

Smilansky 25, Netanya | 050-5937839 | Batelale7@gmail.com

PROFILE

Responsible IT Support Specialist experienced in problem-solving, customer service and good judgment. Ability to complete tasks on time in both individual and team settings.

Dependable and reliable, ready to learn and grow with your company.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

IT SUPPORT (IDF)

Dec 2020 - Dec 2022

- · Provided comprehensive support to customers through CRM system, on-call, and face-to-face.
- · Provided technical support thoroughly during busy times
- · Performed network, software (Windows 10) and hardware troubleshooting to ensure all systems operating optimally.
- · Conducted on-boarding for new soldiers.
- · Assisted in determining requirements and developing plans to ensure smooth installation and documentation of new software and applications.

IT SUPPORT (NOGA - ISRAEL INDEPENDENT SYSTEM OPERATOR)

March 2023 – Today

- · Resolved customer technical issues to ensure all issues are closed in time with the right resolution and highest customer satisfactions
- · Opened tickets and maintained documentation to track tickets through resolution.
- Assisted with user access, creation, editing, and troubleshooting in Active Directory & Office 365 Admin Center.
- · Performed PC and computer installations, setup, and maintenance of hardware and software for new and existing users.
- · Provided expertise to maintain and support various IT systems while adhering to company and department strategies and standards.
- · Managed a successful on-boarding experience for new customers

EDUCATION

"ARIEL" HIGH SCHOOL

Sep 2017 – June 2020

COURSES

NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR (95)

Feb 2021 – April 2021

FULL STACK

Nov 2023 - Current

LANGUAGES

HEBREW

Native speaker

ENGLISH

Fluent